A Guide to the Records of the Drug Policy Office of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1987-1994 (bulk 1990-1994)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Grants, 1987-1994., Extent: 25.90 cu. ft. (74 boxes) (Box 22-94)
  - IDEA, Petersburg, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - IDEA, Pittsylvania County, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - IDEA, Portsmouth, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - IDEA, Portsmouth, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - IDEA, Pulaski, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - IDEA, Richmond (city), 1991 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - IDEA, Richmond (city), 1993 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - IDEA, Winchester, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - John Wayland Elementary School (Bridgewater, Va.), Poster, c. 1990-1994 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - King George County Public Schools, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Lee County Office on Youth-District One, Inc., 1987-1990 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Lee County Office on Youth-District One, Inc., 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 3-4)
  - Loudoun County Youth Shelter, 1989-1991 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Love Outreach Center (Richmond, Va.), 1991 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Lynchburg City Public Schools, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Lynchburg City Public Schools, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Lynchburg YMCA, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Mental Health Services of the Roanoke Valley, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Mothers Inc. (Virginia Beach, Va.), 1990-1992 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - NAADAC (National Association of Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Counselors), 1992 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - National Collegiate Conference, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Newport News Public Schools, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Newport News Public Schools, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Newport News 7th District Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court 1991 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Newport News Police Department, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Newport News Safe Neighborhoods Coalition, 1991-1993 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Norfolk Community Service Board, 1987-1990 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Northampton-Accomack County, Big Brothers Big Sisters, 1989-1991 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - "Parents, Kids, Drugs", Live broadcast, 1991-1993 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Parents Support Center (Norfolk, Va.), 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Patrick Henry Drug and Alcohol Council (Martinsville, Va.), 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - People, Inc., of Southwest Virginia, 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - People, Inc., of Southwest Virginia, 1988-1990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Petersburg Redevelopment and Housing Authority, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Portsmouth Community Service Board, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Portsmouth Community Service Board, 1988-1990 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Portsmouth City Department Parks and Recreation, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Prince William County Community Services Board, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Prince William County Community Services Board, 1988-1990 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Project LINK, College of William and Mary, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Project LINK, Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Substance Abuse Services, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Project LINK, Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Substance Abuse Services, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 3-6)
  - Project LINK, Region Ten Community Service Board (Charlottesville; Albemarle, Fluvanna, Greene, Louisa, and Nelson Counties), 1991 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Project LINK, Virginia Beach Community Service Board, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - PULSAR, Inc., 1991-1993 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - PULSAR (Police, Public Educators, and Peer Counselors Utilizing the Leadership of Students At Risk), Albemarle County, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - PULSAR, Augusta County, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - PULSAR, Bedford County, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - PULSAR, Culpeper County, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - PULSAR, Greene County, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - PULSAR, Madison County, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - PULSAR, Newport News, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - PULSAR, Norfolk, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - PULSAR, Petersburg, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - PULSAR, Richmond, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - PULSAR, Tazewell County, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - PULSAR, Virginia Beach, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - PULSAR, Waynesboro, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - PULSAR, Winchester, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Richmond, Human Services Policy Analyst, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Richmond City Public Schools, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Richmond Community Services Board, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Richmond Youth Services Commission, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Roanoke City Public Schools, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Roanoke City Public Schools, 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Roanoke County Public Schools, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Robert E. Lee High School (Staunton, Va.), 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Rockbridge Area Community Services Board, 1988-1990 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Rockbridge Area Community Services Board, Needs Assessment Study, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Accomack-Northampton Counties, 1993-1994 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Accomack-Northampton Counties, Needs and Risks Assessments, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Buchanan County, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Buckingham County, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Charles City County, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Charles City County, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Charlotte County, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Charlotte County, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Franklin County, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Giles County, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 3-5)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Halifax County, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 6-7)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Halifax County, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Isle of Wight County, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, James City County-Williamsburg, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, King and Queen County, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Lunenburg County, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Lunenburg County, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Smyth County, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Wise County, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Wise County, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Wise County, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Needs and Risk Assessment Project, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 4-6)
  - Rural Grants, Alcohol and Other Drugs of Abuse, Needs and Risk Assessment Project, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
  - St. Gertrude High School (Richmond, Va.), 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
  - St. John's Hospital (Richmond, Va.), 1989-1993 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Scott County Board of Supervisors, 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Scott County Board of Supervisors, 1989-1991 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - ShenanArts, Inc. (Staunton, Va.), 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Southside Community Services Board (Mecklenburg Co., Va.), 1987-1988 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Southside Community Services Board, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 5-6)
  - Sports Virginia, Inc., 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - State Council of Higher Education, Substance Abuse Prevention Program, 1991-1994 (Box 64a, Folder 1-4)
  - Steamer Company No. 5 (Richmond, Va.), 1988-1990 (Box 64a, Folder 5)
  - SAP (Student Assistance Program), Accomack County, 1993-1994 (Box 64a, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Albemarle County, 1991 (Box 64a, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Albemarle County, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Alleghany County, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Amelia County, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - SAP, Amelia County, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Augusta County, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - SAP, Bedford County, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Bedford County, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Botetourt County, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - SAP, Bristol, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - SAP, Campbell County, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - SAP, Charles City County, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - SAP, Charlotte County, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - SAP, Charlotte County, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - SAP, Charlottesville, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Charlottesville, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Chesapeake, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - SAP, Chesterfield County, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Clarke County, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - SAP), Clarke County, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Culpeper County, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Culpeper County, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - SAP, Cumberland County, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - SAP, Danville, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Danville, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Dinwiddie County, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - SAP, Dinwiddie County, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Essex County, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - SAP, Fairfax County, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Falls Church, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Fluvanna County, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - SAP, Franklin City, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - SAP, Franklin County, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - SAP, Frederick County, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Frederick County, 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Gloucester County, 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - SAP, Goochland-Powhatan County, 1991-1992 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Goochland-Powhatan County, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - SAP, Greene County, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Halifax County, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Hampton, 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - SAP, Hanover County, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - SAP, Harrisonburg-Rockingham County, 1991-1992 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - SAP, Henrico County, 1993-1994 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Highland County, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Highland County, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - SAP, King William County, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Lee County, 1993-1994 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - SAP, Loudoun County, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Lunenburg County, 1993-1994 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Lynchburg, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - SAP, Lynchburg, 1993-1994 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - SAP, Madison County, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - SAP, Madison County, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - SAP, Manassas, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - SAP, Manassas, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - SAP, Manassas, 1993-1994 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - SAP, Marion, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Martinsville, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Mathews County, 1991-1992 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - SAP, Mecklenburg County, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Mecklenburg County, 1993-1994 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - SAP, Montgomery County, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Montgomery County, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Montgomery County, 1993-1994 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - SAP, Nelson County, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - SAP, Norfolk, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - SAP, Northampton County, 1993-1994 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - SAP, Nottoway County, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - SAP, Patrick County, 1991-1992 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - SAP, Petersburg, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Portsmouth, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Prince Edward County, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - SAP, Prince Edward County, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Pulaski County, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - SAP, Rappahannock County, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Rappahannock County, 1993-1994 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Richmond (City), 1992 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - SAP, Roanoke (City), 1991 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - SAP, Roanoke (City), 1992 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - SAP, Roanoke County, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - SAP, Roanoke County, 1992-1993 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - SAP, Rockbridge County, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - SAP, Scott County, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - SAP, Smyth County, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Smyth County, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Smyth County, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - SAP, Stafford County, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Staunton, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - SAP, Suffolk, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Suffolk, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Suffolk, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - SAP, Washington County-Highlands, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - SAP, Williamsburg-James City County, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - SAP, Williamsburg-James City County, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Winchester, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Wise County, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - SAP, Wise County, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Wise County, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - SAP, Dept. of Education, 1990-1992 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Review Team, Blank forms, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Review Team, Review checklist, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Charlotte-Charlottesville, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Chesapeake, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Fairfax-Franklion, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Lynchburg-Madison, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Manassas, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Marion-Montgomery, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Petersburg-Portsmouth, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Richmond-Rustburg, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Suffolk, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - SAP, Review Team, Copies of Grants, Williamsburg-Wise, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - SASA (Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault Grants), Higher Education, Christopher Newport University, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - SASA, Higher Education, George Mason University, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - SASA, Higher Education, George Mason University, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Germanna Community College, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - SASA, Higher Education, James Madison University, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - SASA, Higher Education, James Madison University, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - SASA, Higher Education, J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Longwood College, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Lord Fairfax Community College, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Lord Fairfax Community College, 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Mary Washington College, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Mountain Empire Community College, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Mountain Empire Community College, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Norfolk State University, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Old Dominion University, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Patrick Henry Community College, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Patrick Henry Community College, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Paul D. Camp Community College, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Piedmont Community College, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Radford University, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Southwest Virginia Community College, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Thomas Nelson Community College, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Tidewater Community College, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - SASA, Higher Education, University of Virginia, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - SASA, Higher Education, University of Virginia, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Virginia Commonwealth University, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Virginia Commonwealth University, Campus Police, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Virginia Highland Community College, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Virginia State University, 1991-1992 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Virginia State University, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Virginia Tech, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Virginia Tech, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Virginia Western Community College, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - SASA, Higher Education, Wytheville Community College, 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Task Force on Substance Abuse Services for Offenders, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - This Way House (Alexandria, Va.), 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Jefferson High School (Alexandria, Va.), 1989 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Tri-County Medical Corp. of Caroline County, 1988-1989 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Tucker High School PTA (Richmond, Va.), 1989-1990 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - UVA, Institute for Substance Abuse Studies, 1988-1990 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - UVA, Institute for Substance Abuse Studies, Project APPLE, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - UVA, Institute for Substance Abuse Studies, Project VIEW (Virginia Intervention Education Weekend), 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - UVA, Institute for Substance Abuse Studies, Project VIEW, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - UVA, Special Consultant to the Governor on High Risk Youth, Families, and Communities, 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Association of Community Services Board, 1989-1990 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Association of Drug and Alcohol Programs, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Association of Public Television, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Beach, Comprehensive Substance Abuse Program, 1989-1991 (Box 79, Folder 4-7)
  - Virginia Beach, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Cares, Inc. (Roanoke, Va.), 1991 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU), Dept. of Psychology, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - VCU, Dept. of Psychology, 1990-1991 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - VCU, Dept. of Psychology, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - VCU, Medical College of Virginia, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - VCU, Virginia Institute for Development Disabilities (VIDD), A Matter of Substance Training Project (AMOS), 1992-1993 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - VCU-VIDD, AMOS, Perinatal Substance Abuse Training for Care Givers, 1991-1992 (Box 81, Folder 1-2)
  - VCU-VIDD, AMOS, Perinatal Substance Abuse Training for Care Givers, Handout package, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 3-5)
  - VCU-VIDD, AMOS, Perinatal Substance Abuse Training for Care Givers, Handout package, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 1-6)
  - VCU, Substance Abuse Intervention Project, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - VCU and Va. Dept. of Education, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Council on Coordinating Prevention, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Council on Coordinating Prevention, 1990-1992 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Episcopal School (Lynchburg, Va.), 1988-1990 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Federation of Communities for Drug Free Youth, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Heroes, Inc. (Richmond, Va.), 1991 (Box 83, Folder 7-8)
  - Virginia Heroes, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Heroes, Inc., 1993 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Virginia State AFL-CIO, 1991-1992 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - William Byrd Community House (Richmond, Va.), 1988-1989 (Box 84, Folder 4-5)
  - WNVC (Fairfax, Va.), 1990-1991 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #1-6, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #7-10, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #11-18, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #19-25, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #26-33, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #34-39, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #40-42, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #43-53, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #54-60, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #61-65, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #66-67, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #68-70, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #73-78, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #81-89, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, No id #, 1989 July-1991 June (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, Addresses, 1991-1992 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #3-13 1991 July-1992 September (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #15-20, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #21-25, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #26-30, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #31-35, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #36-40, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #41-45, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #46-50, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #54, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #51-55, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #56-60, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #61-65, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #66-70, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #71-75, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #76-80, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #81-85, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #86-90, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #91-95, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #96-100, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - DFSCA, Governor's Programs, Performance reports, #101-105, 1991 July-1992 September (Box 90, Folder 6)